<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Cats Hunt For Fun</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.CatsHuntForFun</packageId>
  <author>Mlie</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/CatsHuntForFun</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/buuPQel.png[/img]

Cats will hunt for fun, not just when they are hungry.

Adds a new activity for cats to hunt when not doing anything else.
The hunting attack is always a surprise attack so the risk for the cat to get hurt is minimal.
Cats will not try to hunt when hurt or downed.
They will also not attack until the prey is downed or killed but can choose to just hit it once and walk away. (Cats are like that)
If the gift-option is active, cats can take a valid prey in any health-state and leave it as a gift to their owner.

There are options in the mod for
- Range to search for prey in
- How likely it is that a cat will attack a prey in range
- How likely it is that a cat will bring a prey in range as a gift to their owner
- Relative body-size to attack
- Hunt only in home area
- To not hunt animals belonging to the player colony
- If wild animals should hunt for fun as well (they will ignore the above limitations regarding area and colony animals)

What animals are considered "Cats" can be selected as well.
There is built in support for some common cat-mods but if anyone is missing you can add it as well.

Or go nuts and enable it for wild thrumbos and try to survive!

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/CatsHuntForFun][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
    [tr]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/WjDSfUn.png[/img][/td]
        [td][img]https://i.imgur.com/h5VwTNL.png[/img][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/O0IIlYj.png[/img]
Since modding is just a hobby for me I expect no donations to keep modding. If you still want to show your support you can gift me anything from my [url=https://store.steampowered.com/wishlist/id/Mlie]Wishlist[/url] or buy me a cup of tea.

[url=https://ko-fi.com/G2G55DDYD][img]https://i.imgur.com/Utx6OIH.png[/img][/url]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/PwoNOj4.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]

</description>
</ModMetaData>